<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>roster Archives - Retro Bowl Unblocked Game</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/roster/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/roster</link>
	<description>Play Unblocked &#38; Free</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:47:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>roster Archives - Retro Bowl Unblocked Game</title>
	<link>/tag/roster</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Retro Bowl Roster: A Comprehensive Wiki</title>
		<link>/retro-bowl-roster</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[New Star Games]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Wiki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nostalgia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[retro bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[roster]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/?p=1039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the Retro Bowl, where football history comes alive! Delve into the comprehensive wiki of Retro Bowl rosters, spanning from the first season to the current one. From iconic quarterbacks to legendary defenders, get ready to relive the glory days of football. The Retro Bowl: A Fusion of Eras Established in 2020, the Retro [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/retro-bowl-roster">Retro Bowl Roster: A Comprehensive Wiki</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Retro Bowl Unblocked Game</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1280" height="720" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster.png 1280w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster-300x169.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster-1024x576.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster-768x432.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster-750x422.png 750w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807472.7266798-retro_bowl_roster-1140x641.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /><p>Welcome to the Retro Bowl, where football history comes alive! Delve into the comprehensive wiki of Retro Bowl rosters, spanning from the first season to the current one. From iconic quarterbacks to legendary defenders, get ready to relive the glory days of football. </p>
<h2>The Retro Bowl: A Fusion of Eras</h2>
<p>Established in 2020, the Retro Bowl is a professional football league that brings together players from different eras. Here, you&#8217;ll find current stars, former greats, and even players from the defunct XFL. Divided into the American Football Conference (AFC) and the National Football Conference (NFC), each team boasts a 53-player roster.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807477.759991-retro_bowl_roster.png" alt="Retro Bowl Roster" /></p>
<h2>Current Retro Bowl Rosters: Unleash the Powerhouses</h2>
<p>Discover the star-studded rosters of the Retro Bowl&#8217;s current season. Let&#8217;s take a closer look at some of the standout teams in each division:</p>
<h3>AFC East</h3>
<p><strong>New England Patriots</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Tom Brady, Cam Newton, Jarrett Stidham</li>
<li>Running Backs: Sony Michel, James White, Rex Burkhead</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Julian Edelman, N’Keal Harry, Damiere Byrd</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Ryan Izzo, Jacob Hollister, Matt LaCosse</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Isaiah Wynn, Joe Thuney, David Andrews</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Lawrence Guy, Adam Butler, Deatrich Wise Jr.</li>
<li>Linebackers: Dont’a Hightower, Jamie Collins, Kyle Van Noy</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Stephon Gilmore, Devin McCourty, Patrick Chung</li>
<li>Special Teams: Jake Bailey, Joe Cardona</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>New York Jets</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Sam Darnold, Joe Flacco, David Fales</li>
<li>Running Backs: Le’Veon Bell, Bilal Powell, Ty Montgomery</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Robby Anderson, Jamison Crowder, Demaryius Thomas</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Ryan Griffin, Daniel Brown, Trevon Wesco</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Kelvin Beachum, Brian Winters, Kelechi Osemele</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Quinnen Williams, Leonard Williams, Steve McLendon</li>
<li>Linebackers: C.J. Mosley, Avery Williamson, Jordan Jenkins</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Trumaine Johnson, Jamal Adams, Darryl Roberts</li>
<li>Special Teams: Lachlan Edwards, Thomas Hennessy</li>
</ul>
<h3>AFC North</h3>
<p><strong>Baltimore Ravens</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Lamar Jackson, Robert Griffin III, Trace McSorley</li>
<li>Running Backs: Mark Ingram, Gus Edwards, Justice Hill</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Marquise Brown, Willie Snead, Miles Boykin</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Mark Andrews, Hayden Hurst, Nick Boyle</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Ronnie Stanley, Marshal Yanda, Orlando Brown Jr.</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Brandon Williams, Michael Pierce, Chris Wormley</li>
<li>Linebackers: Patrick Onwuasor, Matt Judon, Tyus Bowser</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Marlon Humphrey, Earl Thomas, Jimmy Smith</li>
<li>Special Teams: Sam Koch, Justin Tucker</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cincinnati Bengals</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Andy Dalton, Ryan Finley, Jake Dolegala</li>
<li>Running Backs: Joe Mixon, Giovani Bernard, Trayveon Williams</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: A.J. Green, Tyler Boyd, John Ross</li>
<li>Tight Ends: C.J. Uzomah, Tyler Eifert, Drew Sample</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Cordy Glenn, John Miller, Trey Hopkins</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Geno Atkins, Carlos Dunlap, Sam Hubbard</li>
<li>Linebackers: Preston Brown, Germaine Pratt, Nick Vigil</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: William Jackson III, Dre Kirkpatrick, Shawn Williams</li>
<li>Special Teams: Kevin Huber, Randy Bullock</li>
</ul>
<h3>AFC South</h3>
<p><strong>Houston Texans</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Deshaun Watson, A.J. McCarron, Joe Webb</li>
<li>Running Backs: Lamar Miller, Carlos Hyde, Taiwan Jones</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: DeAndre Hopkins, Will Fuller, Kenny Stills</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Darren Fells, Jordan Thomas, Kahale Warring</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Tytus Howard, Max Scharping, Zach Fulton</li>
<li>Defensive Line: J.J. Watt, D.J. Reader, Angelo Blackson</li>
<li>Linebackers: Whitney Mercilus, Benardrick McKinney, Zach Cunningham</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Johnathan Joseph, Bradley Roby, Justin Reid</li>
<li>Special Teams: Bryan Anger, Ka’imi Fairbairn</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Tennessee Titans</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Marcus Mariota, Ryan Tannehill, Logan Woodside</li>
<li>Running Backs: Derrick Henry, Dion Lewis, David Fluellen</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Corey Davis, Adam Humphries, Tajae Sharpe</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Delanie Walker, Jonnu Smith, Anthony Firkser</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Taylor Lewan, Jack Conklin, Rodger Saffold</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Jurrell Casey, DaQuan Jones, Jeffery Simmons</li>
<li>Linebackers: Wesley Woodyard, Jayon Brown, Rashaan Evans</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Malcolm Butler, Logan Ryan, Kevin Byard</li>
<li>Special Teams: Brett Kern, Cairo Santos</li>
</ul>
<h2>Retro Bowl Roster Changes Through the Years</h2>
<p>Since its inception, the Retro Bowl has witnessed remarkable roster changes. Here are some notable highlights from each year:</p>
<h3>2020</h3>
<p>The 2020 Retro Bowl season marked the addition of several new teams, including the Los Angeles Chargers, Las Vegas Raiders, Tampa Bay Buccaneers, and Seattle Seahawks. The season also saw the return of renowned players like Tom Brady to the New England Patriots.</p>
<h3>2021</h3>
<p>The 2021 Retro Bowl season brought in the Arizona Cardinals and the San Francisco 49ers. Notable veterans, including Joe Montana, joined the 49ers, adding to the league&#8217;s legends.</p>
<h3>2022</h3>
<p>The 2022 Retro Bowl season introduced the Jacksonville Jaguars and the Carolina Panthers. The Panthers celebrated the return of Julius Peppers, a true icon of the game.</p>
<h3>2023</h3>
<p>In 2023, the Retro Bowl welcomed the New York Giants and the Washington Football Team to its ranks. Eli Manning, a household name, made a triumphant comeback with the Giants.</p>
<h3>2024</h3>
<p>The 2024 Retro Bowl season witnessed the Detroit Lions and the Cleveland Browns joining the league. Calvin Johnson, a wide receiver extraordinaire, once again graced the field, this time representing the Lions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thumbsretrobowl1686807484.0689187-retro_bowl_roster.png" alt="Retro Bowl Roster" /></p>
<h2>Retro Bowl Expansion Drafts: Building New Legacies</h2>
<p>Throughout the years, the Retro Bowl has conducted expansion drafts to build new teams. Here are some notable expansion drafts that shaped the league:</p>
<h3>2020 Expansion Draft</h3>
<p>Prior to the 2020 season, the Retro Bowl Expansion Draft allowed the Los Angeles Chargers, Las Vegas Raiders, Tampa Bay Buccaneers, and Seattle Seahawks to select five players each from existing teams.</p>
<h3>2021 Expansion Draft</h3>
<p>The 2021 Retro Bowl Expansion Draft preceded the season and gave the Arizona Cardinals and the San Francisco 49ers the opportunity to choose five players each from the league&#8217;s existing teams.</p>
<h3>2022 Expansion Draft</h3>
<p>Before the 2022 season, the Jacksonville Jaguars and the Carolina Panthers participated in the Retro Bowl Expansion Draft, picking five players each from the league&#8217;s established teams.</p>
<h3>2023 Expansion Draft</h3>
<p>In preparation for the 2023 season, the New York Giants and the Washington Football Team held their own Retro Bowl Expansion Draft, selecting five players each from the league&#8217;s pool.</p>
<h3>2024 Expansion Draft</h3>
<p>The 2024 season saw the Detroit Lions and the Cleveland Browns engage in their own Retro Bowl Expansion Draft, choosing five players each from existing teams.</p>
<h2>Retro Bowl All-Time Rosters: Legends in Action</h2>
<p>Behold the all-time rosters of the Retro Bowl, showcasing the greatest players in history. Feast your eyes on the following legendary lineups:</p>
<h3>New England Patriots All-Time Roster</h3>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Tom Brady, Drew Bledsoe, Steve Grogan</li>
<li>Running Backs: Curtis Martin, Corey Dillon, BenJarvus Green-Ellis</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Randy Moss, Wes Welker, Troy Brown</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Rob Gronkowski, Ben Coates, Aaron Hernandez</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: John Hannah, Bruce Armstrong, Logan Mankins</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Richard Seymour, Vince Wilfork, Ty Warren</li>
<li>Linebackers: Tedy Bruschi, Mike Vrabel, Andre Tippett</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Ty Law, Rodney Harrison, Asante Samuel</li>
<li>Special Teams: Adam Vinatieri, Zoltan Mesko</li>
</ul>
<h3>New York Jets All-Time Roster</h3>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Joe Namath, Vinny Testaverde, Richard Todd</li>
<li>Running Backs: Curtis Martin, Freeman McNeil, Matt Snell</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Wayne Chrebet, Al Toon, Keyshawn Johnson</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Mickey Shuler, Rich Caster, Johnny Mitchell</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Winston Hill, Marvin Powell, Kevin Mawae</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Joe Klecko, Mark Gastineau, Shaun Ellis</li>
<li>Linebackers: Mo Lewis, Greg Buttle, Kyle Clifton</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Darrelle Revis, Aaron Glenn, Victor Green</li>
<li>Special Teams: Pat Leahy, Tom Tupa</li>
</ul>
<h3>Baltimore Ravens All-Time Roster</h3>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Joe Flacco, Trent Dilfer, Vinny Testaverde</li>
<li>Running Backs: Ray Rice, Jamal Lewis, Priest Holmes</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Derrick Mason, Anquan Boldin, Mark Clayton</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Todd Heap, Shannon Sharpe, Ben Watson</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Jonathan Ogden, Marshal Yanda, Michael Oher</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Haloti Ngata, Terrell Suggs, Tony Siragusa</li>
<li>Linebackers: Ray Lewis, Peter Boulware, Ed Reed</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Chris McAlister, Samari Rolle, Ed Reed</li>
<li>Special Teams: Matt Stover, Sam Koch</li>
</ul>
<h3>Cincinnati Bengals All-Time Roster</h3>
<ul>
<li>Quarterbacks: Boomer Esiason, Ken Anderson, Jeff Blake</li>
<li>Running Backs: Corey Dillon, Rudi Johnson, James Brooks</li>
<li>Wide Receivers: Chad Johnson, Carl Pickens, Cris Collinsworth</li>
<li>Tight Ends: Bob Trumpy, Dan Ross, Rodney Holman</li>
<li>Offensive Linemen: Anthony Munoz, Max Montoya, Willie Anderson</li>
<li>Defensive Line: Tim Krumrie, Reggie Williams, Justin Smith</li>
<li>Linebackers: Takeo Spikes, Brian Simmons, David Fulcher</li>
<li>Defensive Backs: Ken Riley, Louis Breeden, Lemar Parrish</li>
<li>Special Teams: Lee Johnson, Kevin Huber</li>
</ul>
<h2>In Conclusion</h2>
<p>This comprehensive wiki has provided you with an exclusive glimpse into the Retro Bowl rosters, from the past to the present. You&#8217;ve traveled through time, witnessing the evolution of teams and marveling at the greatness of football legends. Stay tuned for more captivating content, and continue immersing yourself in the magic of the Retro Bowl.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://i.imgur.com/5708QsF.png" alt="Thanks for reading" /></p>
<p>The post <a href="/retro-bowl-roster">Retro Bowl Roster: A Comprehensive Wiki</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Retro Bowl Unblocked Game</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
